
Name: Financial Client Registration App
Goal: A simple Java application to register and manage business clients with basic contact information.
Audience: Beginner to intermediate Java students learning OOP, file I/O, validation, and data management.

Client; A financiel accountancy officer. The app will be used by people inside of the company.

Type of app: Console application. We do not have a frontend, only interaction through the terminal. 
We are backend developer

Customer: 

Must-Have Features (Core Functional Requirements)
1. Register a client (firstname, lastname, bsuinessname, e-mailadress and phonenumbers
2. View clients (display a list of all registered clients)
	 Format the clients name like this: Lastname, Firstname and initials. 
3.  Save the data -> Store client data in a text file / csv file (which is normally a SQL database)

Nice to have features:
Search clients based on image (AI?) -> Search by name
Export the data to a CSV file.